https://www.booksandpublishing.com.au/privacy/

Moves/personnel
Place a classified, notice, agency change or personnel notice
Privacy policy
Books and Publishing Pty Ltd (ABN 68 627 053 098) owns and operates the Books+Publishing website (formerly operated by Thorpe-Bowker).
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please contact us by sending an email to subscriptions@booksandpublishing.com.au or writing to the Publisher at the above postal address.
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy Books and Publishing provides this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home pages and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. This notice applies to all information collected from or submitted to all Books and Publishing websites.
Participation on our websites
By using our websites, you consent to the collection, use and storage of your information by us in the manner described in this Privacy Policy and elsewhere on our websites.
Data gathering, usage and storage
User information is held on both Australian and overseas servers. Books and Publishing collects the contact details and email addresses of subscribers of our products and the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email. We collect information on pages that users visit via Google Analytics, for statistical and usage information, however this is view is an aggregated result and a single-user view is not available. We collect information on login attempts by users. We collect information through survey forms to improve the content of our websites or create news stories. We use MailChimp to send newsletters to subscribers, which has explains its data protection rules here. The user information that we collect, may be used for marketing purposes to inform users of other Books and Publishing products or services they may be interested in and users who provide their mailing address, telephone number, or email address may be contacted for these purposes. The information we collect may also be disclosed to a third party for marketing purposes.
Cookies
An electronic ‘cookie’ is an identity code that is placed on a subscriber’s browser to enable Books+Publishing website to recognise the subscriber and allow them to stay logged in. The cookie will stay active for two weeks, then after the cookie disappears, the subscriber will have to login again, which will create a new cookie. Without cookies, subscribers will not be able to login. By clicking the ‘login’ button, you are accepting to allow cookies to identify your browser and keep you logged in.
We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies or third party advertising agencies that track certain Internet activity.
Future changes to privacy policy
From time to time, we may use information collected and supplied by users for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our websites to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.
If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should refer to this online privacy policy page periodically.
Opt-out
Visitors and subscribers who have supplied us with information may elect not to receive email, postal or telephone communications from Books and Publishing and/or other organisations this information is shared with by emailing us at the above address or writing to us at the above postal address.
Access, correct or delete your information
Upon request, we can provide subscribers with the information that we maintain about them or delete the information. However, if we delete the information, the subscriber will no longer be able to hold a subscription. Subscribers may correct their contact information, by logging in and editing their contact details on the login page. We don’t hold information about visitors to the website, who are not paying or complementary subscribers and have not provided their email address.
Data security
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected on our site. Passwords are not stored as plain text and this is why we can’t provide a subscriber with their current password, but subscribers can request a link to be emailed to update their password here.
Outside links
Books and Publishing has provided several hyperlinks to outside resources in an effort to help individuals gather information. Books and Publishing is not responsible for the content provided on these sites, their privacy policies, or how they treat information about their users. Some hyperlinks, primarily to book industry sites and entities, are provided as a service to our users. Other hyperlinks to suppliers are available as part of paid advertising packages.
Home
About
Contact us
Editorial submissions
B+P announcements
History
Magazine numbering
Archive
Moves/personnel
Place a classified, notice, agency change or personnel notice
Libraries
Library news
International library news
Publications
Books+Publishing magazine
Think Australian
Newsletters
Recently published by B+P
Advertise
Place a classified or job ad
Magazine or online display advertising
Book Buzz promotional newsletter
This website uses cookies to enhance your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
